[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many species of earthworm are native to Australia?", "correct_answer": "650", "incorrect_answers": ["450", "250", "850"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jenin is the largest city in the West Bank.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What time of year do nutrias breed?", "correct_answer": "All year round", "incorrect_answers": ["In the winter months", "In the Fall", "In the spring"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Crepe is the name of a thin French pancake. What is the meaning of the Latin word crispa from which the name of the dish originated?", "correct_answer": "Curled", "incorrect_answers": ["Thin", "Flat", "Crispy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who were the star-crossed lovers from West Side Story ?", "correct_answer": "Tony and Maria", "incorrect_answers": ["Nardo and Anita", "Juan and Juanita", "Jose and Jorge"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following animals is the odd one?", "correct_answer": "Ram", "incorrect_answers": ["Hen", "Doe", "Vixen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What important vitamin do button mushrooms, a.k.a. common mushrooms, contain?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Vitamin D", "Vitamin B3", "Vitamin B5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Boza is a thick, fermented beverage with a sweet and sour taste. It is made from millet seed and various astringent substances and was invented in which country?", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["Bulgaria", "Greece", "Macedonia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does Bonds wife, Tracy Draco, die at the end of the film On Her Majestys Secret Service?", "correct_answer": "She is shot by a submachine gun.", "incorrect_answers": ["She is caught in an avalanche.", "She is poisoned  by a glass of wine.", "She falls from a ski lift."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The skin goes purple and waxy about one hour from time of death.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Rockys original trainer returns in Rocky Balboa to help prepare him for his exhibition fight.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this movie, John Wayne played the sheriff of a small town, who has to hold in jail the brother of a powerful rancher. The movie was directed by Howard Hawks.", "correct_answer": "Rio Bravo", "incorrect_answers": ["The Horse Soldiers", "The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance", "Neath The Arizona Skies"]}]